Potlacheruvu Goutham Reddy

Application Development Associate

Graduated from Lovely Professional University in the year 2020 and joined Accenture Solutions Pvt Ltd in the year 2021 as Application Development Associate and trained latest technologies, working towards my passion for the growth of my organization.

p.goutham.reddy@accenture.com

Hyderabad

+91 8096645316

Linkdin.com/in/Goutham Reddy Potlacheruvu

EDUCATION

State Secondary Education A.P

Revathi High school

06/2013 - 03/2014,

9.5 GPA

Intermediate Education T.S

Narayana Institutions

08/2014 - 03/2016,

96.3%

Electronics and Communication Engineering (B.Tech)

Lovely Professional University

07/2016 - 08/2020,

7.52 CGPA

WORK EXPERIENCE

Application Development AssociateAccenture Solutions Pvt Ltd.

04/2021 - Present.

Trainings

o DataScience, Azure, Windows deployment.

Application Development AssociateAccenture Solutions Pvt Ltd.

04/2021 - Present,

Data validation testing

Oata Validation testing is a process that allows the user to check that the provided data, they deal with, is valid or complete. In simple words, data validation is a part of Database testing, in which individual checks that the entered data valid or not according to the provided business condition and also windows deployment and trouble shooting.

Intern

Lovely Professional University

05/2018 - 08/2018,

Weather Monitoring System.

 This is a simple weather monitoring system powered by Arduino UNO, this system detects environmental parameters such as temperature, humidity, barometric pressure and air quality.

SKILLS

DataScience

Java

Azure(cloud)

Adobe Photoshop

PERSONAL PROJECTS

Accelerometer Based Hand Gestured Controlled Robot With ATmega 16 (08/2017 - 12/2017)

Oundergone 3 months of industrial training at RCPL. The project is to control a machine with the movement of hand, sometimes it is quite hard to control a machine with remote or switch and a button. With the help of AVR ATmega16 microcontroller and DC motor driver(L233D) And some basic components this project is made. Hand gestures is taken as input and ATmega16 controller process the signal to machine and Hence this machine follows those commands and works according to it.

Ivanti Management Console (08/2021 - Present)

o Ivanti is an assest management software system used to remotely Inventory and manage desktop computers.it has the ability to repor t on installed software and hardware, allow assistance, and install security patches.

CERTIFICATES

Azure Fundamentals (06/2021 –Present)

Fundamentals of HTML, CSS, JavaScript (06/2020 - Present)

Certified Data Scientist by Upgrad Education (01/2021 - Present)

Introduction to Programming Using Java by Udemy (05/2019 –Present)

LANGUAGES

English

Hindi

• • • • •

Telugu